(Sheldon:)Fancy a dip, my dear?
(Leonard:)I do.
(gasps)
(Sheldon:)Wait, that purple
flag indicates
(Sheldon:)that marine pests, such
as jellyfish, are present.
(Amy:)Wow, that flag
is a lifesaver.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)This is.
(Sheldon:)Stop looking at my legs.
(Sheldon:)Not a flag.
Flag.
(dinging)
(Sheldon:)Flag.
Not a flag.
(buzz)
(groans)
Crap.
(Raj:)When stuff
like this gets me down,
(Raj:)you know what I like to do?
Sing "Hakuna Matata"
like an eight-year-old girl?
(Raj:)Wrong, smarty-pants.
It's "Everything Is Awesome"
from The Lego Movie.
(Leonard:)Look at these notebooks.
(Leonard:)They're full of pages and pages
of data.
(Leonard:)He clearly spent years on this.
Mmm. Oh, it's just columns
of random numbers. Toss it.
(Leonard:)Well, but what if this was a
potential breakthrough for him?